for sure showed a lot of interest
throughout the draft process um
especially at pro day. So uh I had a
good feeling um throughout the draft
about the Bills and was just hoping to
hear my name called and you know I was
happy to hear today.
>> What do you know about your new
quarterback Josh Allen?
>> One of the best ever man he he's doing
at a high high level. Um you know he he
does it with the best of them and you
know I can't wait to work with him.
>> Congratulations Kyler. Enjoy this day.
>> I appreciate it.
Choose Wookie Hawkins Wo Sports Tanetti.
Man, what what what took so long,
>> man? That's that's what I'm wondering
too, man. It's all good though. It's all
good, though.
>> Yeah, perfect timing. Time perfect
timing for this, but just just talk
about your path and what it's been like
getting to this point and what really
has shaped you as a player.
>> Man, just the hard work. Um, obviously,
I thank God first and obviously my
family, my support system, but it's all
in the work. Um, I'm a hard worker. I
just put in the work and just put my
head down, keep grinding, just take it
day by day.
>> What um how would you describe your game
to people who haven't seen you play?
>> I would say I'm dynamic. I'm explosive.
I'm versatile. Uh I could do a lot of
different things inside, outside, heat
ball, contested catches, uh intermediate
games. So, I think I could do a lot of
different things.
>> What it's like uh reuniting with Coach
Lennon? I know you had a brief stint
with him out there in Wisconsin. So,
what it's like reuniting with that guy,
>> man, I I I honestly can't wait to see
him, man. I'm probably going to give him
the craziest hug ever, man. Cuz that
that's my guy, man. I spent a lot of
time with him. I love him to death, man.
He helped me he helped me with my
development a lot my my freshman year
and my sophomore year. So, you know, I
can't wait to see him.
>> How would you be able to create
separation versus physical corners in
the NFL?
I think with my physicality, my body, my
ability to to be able to move and
separate and move my body,
deceptiveness, uh my elusiveness and
just in and out of breaks, uh aggressive
into brakes, aggressive out of brakes,
and speed out of brakes.
>> All right, Juice, you're finally a
Buffalo Bill. Congrats and see you soon.
>> Yes, sir. Go Bills Mafia.
>> Hi, Skyler. I'm Sal Kapacio from WJR
Radio in Buffalo. How are you?
>> How you doing? I'm good.
>> I'm good. um when your name came across.
I think a lot of us here, people in
Buffalo might be fans of Syracuse. I
went to Syracuse. You torched Syracuse
in September. I remember that game. What
do you remember about it,
>> man? I I I I do remember we lost, but
other than that, man, I was having a
day, man. And I I wish I wish we could
have came out with the win, but you
know, I I thought I proved myself to
them boys.
>> Well, I'm kind of glad we beat you in
overtime there, right? But hey, man,
welcome back. Welcome coming up here. I
got to ask you, though. I see uh you
competed in hockey. you're going to fit
well in here in Western New York. Tell
us about your hockey background.
>> Yeah, I'm I'm a huge huge hockey fan,
man. It was my main sport growing up. My
mom got me into it when I was around
five, and I never looked back. I stopped
playing when I was probably around 15,
16, but hockeyy's really my first love.
I still watch the NHL. I'm tapped into
the playoffs right now.
>> And the um the Bills, they have a bit of
a history of selecting guys from Yukon
really over the last several years. And
um I know Ryan Vandermark's one who's
now no longer on the team, but um what
what was your interaction with them
either in the season with anybody you
knew from the organization or when it
started in the pre-draft process?
>> Uh well, one of my one of my teammates,
Chase L, one of my teammates, Chase L is
up there. So I talked to him briefly um
throughout the season and a little bit
before the pre-draw process. Just he was
wishing me good luck and just, you know,
everything's going to take care of
itself. But nothing too crazy. Um I'm
just glad to reunite with him now. How
cool is it going to be to play with
Chase again?
>> Super cool, man. He great teammate,
great great person, you know, great
player.
>> All right, thanks a lot. Congratulations
to you again. We'll see you up here.
>> Thank you. I appreciate it.
>> Yeah.
>> Hey, Skyler, mattyuse.com.
Congratulations.
>> Thank you. Thank you. I appreciate it.
>> Um, can you take me back to uh Jim
Leonard, and you mentioned how much he
helped you grow as a player while at
Wisconsin. Can can you give us a little
insight into what he what he did and and
how those that relationship helped you
improve?
>> Yeah, I mean my my true my true freshman
year I red shirted so I was doing a lot
of scout team stuff and he was our DC so
I was running the routes against his
defense for that week and you know
sometimes I I go up to his office and we
watch the tape and you know he's trying
to get me better. He's telling me things
to work on that I could be better to you
know torch his defense to get them
better and it's just a revolving door a
little bit of everybody making each
other better. So, I think his knowledge
of the game and his ability just to, you
know, help me even from the defensive
side of the ball was was huge for me.
>> And then your skill set, you talked
about being able to kind of be inside
and outside
coming to the NFL and in this wide
receiver room in particular, you think
about DJ Moore, Khalil Shakir, guys that
can kind of do that. Is that something
that the Bills were excited about
because, you know, you kind of fit their
mold of receiver?
>> Yes, sir. I think my versatility
provides a lot of different things that
you could do with me. um um you know,
inside, outside, deep ball, uh
intermediate, short route. So, I think
you know, you have a lot of guys like
that, like you mentioned, the guys that
are already there. I think it, you know,
gives us another element.
>> Awesome. Thank you so much.
>> Thank you.